pixelgroovy.com 2007-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Pixel Groovy

## Privacy Policy

Pixel Groovy knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the pixelgroovy.com, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

  1. #### What Does the Pixel Groovy Privacy Policy Cover?

> This Privacy Policy covers Pixel Groovy's treatment of personal information that Pixel Groovy gathers when you are on pixelgroovy.com. 

> This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Pixel Groovy does not own or control, or to individuals that Pixel Groovy does not employ or manage. 

  2. #### What Personal Information About Users Does Pixel Groovy Collect?

> Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. We collect the following types of information from our users: 

> 1\. Information You Provide to Us: 
>
>> We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as: 
>> 
>> Registration: In order for you to use Pixel Groovy services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require your email address. 
> 
> 2\. Automatic Information: 
>
>> Profile information: Pixel Groovy allows other users to browse your full name, and instant messaging URL, within your member profile should you provide this optional information. 
>> 
>> Syndication: Pixel Groovy allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website. 

  3. #### What About Cookies?

> Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer.s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Pixel Groovy cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is. 

> Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

  4. #### Will Pixel Groovy Share Any of the Information it Receives?

> Pixel Groovy will not share personal information with anyone whether it be on a small or large scale. Information such as passwords and other information which is deemed private will remain private. Pixel Groovy reserves the right to "deem" what is private. 

  5. #### Is Information About Me Secure?

> Your Pixel Groovy account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. 

> Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to it. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. 

  6. #### What Choices Do I Have?

> As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website, such as posting new links. 
> 
> You may request deletion of your Pixel Groovy account by emailing admin@pixelgroovy.com with the email address listed under the account.
